fastway.co.za 2018-09-02

# FASTWAY

                           FASTWAY COURIERS – PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy and Protection of Personal Information
Fastway Couriers understands that privacy is important to you, and is committed to taking all
reasonable steps to protect the personal information of visitors to our website.
For the purposes hereof “personal information” shall be as defined in the Protection of Personal
Information Act, No 4 of 2013.
What personal information does Fastway Couriers collect?
The personal information we will collect from you generally includes your name, surname, sending
address, delivery address, email address and contact numbers – these are not compulsory. We do not
collect personal information that we do not need. Our website does not use persistent cookies.
Why does Fastway Couriers collect personal information?
We collect this information so that:
     1) we can respond to any enquiry we might receive from you;
     2) we can provide information on our franchise opportunities, news, information, products and
         services and to conduct our business;
     3) there is confirmation that you are aware of our conditions of carriage.
What does Fastway Couriers do with the personal information?
Fastway Couriers uses it for the purposes set out in the previous paragraph.
Fastway Couriers does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties.
Fastway Couriers will not disclose your personal information to a third party unless required by law.
Security
Fastway Couriers takes reasonable steps to ensure the security of your personal information. The data
is stored in secure servers located outside of South Africa. Our anti‐virus software is frequently
updated to protect our systems from computer viruses. Further, all Fastway Couriers employees are
required, as a condition of employment, to treat personal information held by Fastway Couriers as
confidential. However, you should be aware that the internet is not a secure environment. We cannot
protect personal information before it reaches us.
Accuracy of information
It is your responsibility to ensure that the information you provide is accurate and complete. If
appropriate, it is also your responsibility to ensure that your personal information is kept up to date.
Privacy Policy
You have the right to ask us to update or correct your personal information when it is inaccurate,
incomplete or out of date. If your personal details change, or you believe the information we hold
about you is incorrect, please contact us so that we can update our records. We retain your personal
information only for so long as required by law.
Contact Details
You have the right to seek access to your personal information handled by Fastway Couriers.
If you would like to contact us about any matter relating to privacy, our details are:
Email: admin@fastway.co.za
Fax: (011) 234 4777
Telephone: (011) 234 9393
Postal: PO Box 663, Rivonia, 2128
 Our Privacy Policy was last updated on 6 January 2017
